JEFFERSON CARAGAY

A beginning intern who has an experienced in IT field, finding a company to enhance my skills and knowledge in IT industry to perform well. Contribute to company with my ideas, sharing techniques as well to lead the way achieving the company's goal.



EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2022

Web Development

 Manage system architecture, website design, programming, decision-making to enhance the reliability of the web and make it user friendly.

2021 - 2022

Database

 Problem-solving tasks to maintain and secure the information through database, to manipulate sensitive information and to track down specific informations.

2020 - 2021

Java language

 Programs a software-based application that will be used through in IT industry, solving a specific task to invent or innovate systems.

2022 - 2023

Android Development

 Can Design and develop programs in android studio using Java and Kotlin, having a knowledge of connecting database to my app such as Firebase.

CONTACT

- **1** 0966 249 7423
- caragayjefferson2@gmail.com
- mww.linkedin.com/in/jefferson-caragay-

5b7489215

Barangay Culiat, Sagana mabilog Quezon

EDUCATION

2016 - 2019

Jose Rizal Institute

STEM

2019 - present

New Era University

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

CERTIFICATIONS

- Cybersecurity Training Program (CTF)
- NoSQL and DBaaS 101
- Big Data 101
- Analytics 101 for Businesses

SKILLS

Good communication 60% Programming 80% Database 75% Web Development 80% Multitasking 90%